# JAMIE R. MORRIS



## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Vision-driven change agent with record of successful remote work for leading organizations

Full-Stack Web Developer currently proficient in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, JQuery, Ajax, APIs. Expertise spanning administrative assistance, web formatting, proofreading/editing, ESL instruction, social media marketing, content management, client relationship management. Exceptionally dedicated professional with keen interpersonal, communication, and organizational skills. Helpful in extending website navigation and product understanding to customers and co-workers.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Astrologer Coach: Sonja Francis (Virtual), December 2015 - Current

### REMOTE ADMINISTRATIVE/SOCIAL MEDIA ASSISTANT

- Schedule social media posts for the public via Hootsuite.
- Compose blog outlines; perform email data entry and list building on GetResponse.com.
- Address customer responses via Ipage email.
- Format, edit, and proofread WordPress page.

COPPERSMITH (VIRTUAL), December 2016 - April 2019

#### REMOTE ECOMMERCE PRODUCT SPECIALIST

- Promoted and sold products to existing and prospective customers.
- Collaborated with a cross-functional group of Marketing, Product, Customer Service, and Operations teams.
- Oversaw administrative functions and special projects using Magento, Zendesk Talk, and Google Apps.
- Updated and maintained existing products, optimizing them to improve the conversion rate and customer experience.

RICHARD JARMINSKI PROPERTY MANAGEMENT, DANA POINT, CA, January 2012 - May 2015

#### **ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT**

- Supported administrative operations for a personal injury lawyer and property investor.
- Generated P&L sheets; prepared and filed tax/accounting forms for investment properties.
- Drafted emails; performed data entry.

Noble Wealth Systems/Gracie Barra, Irvine, CA, October 2011 - April 2014

## **MARKETING ASSISTANT**

- Updated social media marketing channels.
- Coordinated content management with operations department.
- Performed administrative duties.
- Aligned internal communication using Google Apps and Evernote.

### **EDUCATION AND CREDENTIALS**

24-week Certificate of completion FullStack Web Development (expected, 2020) University of New Hampshire, Portsmouth, NH

BACHELOR OF ARTS (B.A.) IN PSYCHOLOGY, 2014 California State University, Fullerton, CA

TEFL Certified, 2015 i-to-i TEFL, 120 hours

Web Design Certificate, in Progress (Expected, 2019) Northern Essex Community College, Haverhill, MA

Jamie R. Morris Page 2

# Awards, Professional Affiliations, Volunteerism

- Landmark Education, Irvine, CA, January 2010 August 2012
- Dean's List Fall 2014, California State University, Fullerton, CA
- Careerwise (Non-Profit), Fullerton, CA, August 2014 March 2015
- Tefl Teacher, Anubaan Chiang Mai School, Chiang Mai, Thailand, May 2015 July 2016

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

**Technical Proficiencies:** Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook), Harms Software Millennium edition, QuickBooks, Magento, Adobe, 60 WPM, 10 Key, Excel, Constant Contact, Facebook, Twitter, Blogger, Wordpress, Kajabi, Zendesk, Zendesk Talk, Get Response, Google Apps, Hootsuite, Canva, Kajabi, html, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, JQuery

**Interests:** Hiking, Running, Martial Arts (Jiu Jitsu), Camping, Backpacking, Volunteering, Art/Drawing, Animal Sanctuaries and Rescues

References available upon request